

Erin Goforth 151 Surf Way Apt. 33 Monterey, CA 93940

(949) 981.8772 Egoforth@csumb.edu

### Objectives

I am a Graphic and Web Designer/ Producer with 2+ years of experience. My positive attitude and determination are what make me accomplish every task. I am able to bring an immense understanding of design concepts and ideas to a future job. I have a strong work ethic and enjoy working in a team or on solo projects.

#### Education

### California State University, Monterey Bay August 2009 - May 2014

- Degree in Communication Design, emphasis in Visual and Web Design
- Minored in Business, emphasis in Marketing
- GPA 3.79
- Dean's List and Magna Cum Laude

#### Experience

#### Independently Contracted Graphic Designer

May 2012 - Present

- I have created many different graphic identities (logo, print materials, and web design) for companies.
- Worked in house and remote.
- Utilized Adobe Creative Suite, Twitter Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, and Drupal

# Information Technology & Web Student Assistant March 2012 - Present

- Help students with any technical issue on their personal computers or the university computers.
- Install software programs & clean virus/malware infected computers
- Help create & build the pages for csumb.edu website

## Sales Associate/Cashier, Sport Chalet Sporting Goods May 2007-2013

- · Assisted customers and gained a greater understanding of them and the community
- Utilized SAP and POS systems
- Cross-trained in all areas of the store, and obtained certified pro pins after passing the tests for each department

#### Skills

- Adobe Creative Suite (Primarily Illustrator, InDesign, & Photoshop)
- Knowlege of HTML, CSS, Drupal, & Twitter Bootstrap
- Microsoft Office
- Knowledge of both Mac and PC Operating Systems
- File Organization
- Information Technology (I.T) Technician